React Native ASS Video Player Demo
Welcome to the comprehensive .ass subtitle demonstration!
This player supports full .ass formatting with precise timing.
Bold text and italic text are fully supported.
Green text, red text, and cyan text!
Large text and small text with spacing.
Different styles like this narrator voice are supported.
Emphasis style with bold, italic, and scaling!
Underlined text and strikethrough text.
Positioned text at specific coordinates.
Left aligned text
Center aligned text
Right aligned text
Rotated text and horizontally scaled.
Semi-transparent text back to opaque.
Multiple colored and styled words in one line.
Subtitles remain perfectly synchronized during seeking!
This works seamlessly on Web, iOS, and Android platforms.
Thank you for watching the demo!